searchengine.com 2016-06-18

# Privacy Policy | BoxOnline Is A Swiss Based Incubator For Startup Technology Ventures

**Last updated: March 3, 2014.**

Thank you for visiting a BoxOnline managed website. Your interest in BoxOnline, our offers, and our ventures is much appreciated. We run a portfolio of websites that include TabletPublisherPro.com, KinetiZine.com, and more than 200 others referred to herein as “this website”. You likely arrived at this Privacy Policy from one of the websites in our portfolio.

This Privacy Policy is subject to change by BoxOnline at any time and at our discretion without notice by updating this posting.

**By visiting this website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.**

Please read this Privacy Policy before using this website or submitting any personal information. California residents, please also see the “Note To California Residents” Section for additional rights that apply to you.

By using this website, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit this website to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

We take Children’s Privacy very seriously. Our Terms & Conditions only allow this website to be accessed by persons eighteen (18) years or older. Due to the age restrictions of this website, none of the information obtained by this website falls within the Child Online Privacy Act (COPA). However, if your minor child has provided us with personally identifiable information, you may contact us at the phone number or mailing address listed in Section seven herein if you want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to remove your child’s information from the database that stores the information.

**1\. Information We Collect**  
**A. Personally Identifiable Information**

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; and (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the website or product(s).

We may disclose personally identifiable information collected if we have received your permission beforehand (such as to fulfill a third party order) or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or for other special cases described below.

We may also periodically conduct surveys of our subscribers and customers from time to time so we can improve on the products and services that we provide. We may from time to time offer you the opportunity to participate in sweepstakes, product giveaways and similar services. You will be asked to provide membership information to participate in any sweepstakes or giveaways. We or a company selected by us administers the sweepstakes and contacts the winner. All sweepstakes are optional.

By permitting us to collect this information, you will be able to receive information on products and services that may be of interest to you, including related third party offers that we may send to you. You also enable us to personalize your experience with us so that we can provide you with the highest quality of service. We may also use this information to contact you about joint venture opportunities if it appears that you would be a suitable joint venture partner.

By submitting your email address on this website, you agree to receive email from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do. By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for custom audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us.

In addition, you agree that by submitting your telephone contact information on this web site and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.  
**B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We also may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information to help us make your experience more enjoyable, measure site activity to identify future improvements that should be made, and compile aggregate data to help serve site visitors better. For example, we may use such data to tailor our advertisements, develop proper survey questions, improve our business, etc.

As another example, we may use session and persistent “cookies,” session logs, web beacons, GIF/pixel tags, banner ads, third-party click tracking analytics tools (such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html "Google Privacy Policy")), third party retargeting networks that may display our advertisements to you on other sites that you visit to remind you about us, and third party networks that serve user-requested emails (e.g., for a refer-a-friend email) to collect non-personally identifiable or other aggregated information about site visitors.

Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our web site.

Emails or newsletters that we send electronically may use techniques such as web beacons or pixel tags to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience, such as the number of emails that are opened, whether they were forwarded or printed, the type of device from which they were opened, the time spent within the content, the elements clicked, and the location (e.g. city, state, and county) associated with the applicable IP address.

If you visit this site with an open ID (such as Facebook), you may also be sharing and integrating data with third-party social media sites, and we may track aggregate data about the number of visits to this site with an open ID, the number of items “liked” on this site, or items on this site that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.

Other parties such as advertising partners and analytics companies may also be collecting information about your online activity across various websites over time. The information collected by those third parties may include identifiers that allow those third parties to tailor the ads that they serve to your computer or other device.

Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals that are undefined.

Please note that you do have the option to configure most web browsers to NOT accept cookies. However, be aware that disabling cookies may keep you from having access to some functions or services on our web site or the web-hosted software that runs on our web site.  
**C. Permission To Use Your Content**

By transmitting any suggestions, comments, information, identification, material, or other content (“content”) to us, you automatically grant us the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, redistribute, transmit, perform and display such content (in whole or part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media, or technology now known or later developed for the full term of any rights that may exist in such content. Further, we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, techniques, and suggestions contained in any communications you send to this website for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to creating, manufacturing, and marketing products and/or services using such information.

We limit access to information about you to employees who need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your account information is password-protected.

**2\. Third Party Actions**

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of any third parties who we may promote. We pride ourselves in working with quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

**3.Cookies**

We may use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests. Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with this website.

**4\. IP Addresses**

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

**5\. Third Party Web Sites**

This website and/or the products and/or services offered herein may direct you to websites that are owned and/or controlled by third parties. We have no control over those third parties and are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of those sites or companies.

We use Paypal, Amazon, Apple and Stripe for all online financial transactions. BoxOnline has no access to your financial information nor do we store any financial information – Both Stripe and Paypal have one of the most secure forms of online transaction available and their services are used for your protection. Please review [Paypal’s Privacy Policy](http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside "Paypal Privacy Notice") and [Stripe’s Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy "Stripe Privacy Policy") and [Apple’s Privacy Policy](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/ "Apple Privacy Policy") and [Amazon’s Privacy ](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496 "Amazon Privacy Notice")Notice prior to making a purchase should you have any concerns.

**6\. Commitment to Data Security**

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**7\. Contacting Us**

If you need to contact us, you can use the form on http://boxonline.com/contact-us/ or for support related issues http://support.boxonline.com

We strive to provide excellent services, superb products, and equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.

**8\. Note To California Residents**

If you live in the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that companies who conduct business in California provide you with a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes.

Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a Privacy Policy that gives either an opt-out (often referred to as “unsubscribe”) or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, that the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

This website qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.

If you are a California resident and want to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Please submit a message to the Privacy Administrator at http://support.boxonline.com, or you may contact us via regular mail at: BoxOnline, Bahnhofstr 23, 6301 Zug, Switzerland.

**All requests sent via regular mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request.** For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code.

****We do not accept requests via telephone or fax.** We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.**
